(gentle music)
♪ Do you remember ♪
♪ The 21st night of September ♪
♪ Love was changin' the
minds of pretenders ♪
♪ While chasin' the clouds away ♪
♪ Our hearts were ringin' ♪
♪ In the key that our souls were singin' ♪
♪ As we danced in the night, remember ♪
♪ How the stars stole the
night away, oh, yeah ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ Ba-dee-ya, say, do you remember ♪
♪ Ba-dee-ya, dancin' in September ♪
♪ Ba-dee-ya, never was a cloudy day ♪
♪ Ba-du-da, ba-du-da, ba-du-da, ba-du ♪
♪ Ba-du-da, ba-du, ba-du-da, ba-du ♪
♪ Ba-du-da, ba-du, ba-du-da ♪
♪ My thoughts are with you ♪
♪ Holdin' hands with
your heart to see you ♪
♪ Only blue talk and love, remember ♪
♪ How we knew love was here to stay ♪
♪ Now December ♪
♪ Found the love that
we shared in September ♪
♪ Only blue talk and love, remember ♪
♪ The true love we share today ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ Ba-dee-ya, say, do you remember ♪
♪ Ba-dee-ya, dancin' in September ♪
♪ Ba-dee-ya, never was a cloudy day ♪
♪ There was a ♪
♪ Ba-dee-ya dee-ya, dee-ya,
say, do you remember ♪
dancin' in September ♪
♪ Ba-dee-ya dee-ya, dee-ya,
golden dreams were shiny days ♪
♪ The bell was ringin', oh, oh ♪
♪ Our souls were singin' ♪
♪ Do you remember never a cloudy day Yow ♪
♪ There was a ♪
♪ Ba-dee-ya dee-ya, dee-ya,
say, do you remember ♪
dancin' in September ♪
♪ Ba-dee-ya dee-ya, dee-ya,
never was a cloudy day ♪
♪ And we'll say ♪
♪ Ba-dee-ya dee-ya, dee-ya,
say, do you remember ♪
dancin' in September ♪
♪ Ba-dee-ya dee ya, dee-ya,
golden dreams were shiny days ♪
♪ Ba-dee-ya, dee-ya, dee-ya ♪
♪ Ba-dee-ya, dee-ya, dee-ya, dee-ya ♪